amerikanki.com 2015-09-15

# Privacy Policy | Lifestyle

We understand the great importance of your privacy and we protect it when you visit our site and when you contact us. The following Privacy Policy will explain our online information practices and the choices which you can take about the way your personal information is gathered and used. You can always access the Privacy Policy, since it’s available on our homepage any time when you visit Amerikanki.com and all subdomains. Also if you are taking care about your privacy online, please read our [Disclaimer](http://en.amerikanki.com/disclaimer/).

**Google Adsense Cookie**  
As a third party ad vendor, Google uses cookies to serve advertisements on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookies enables them to serve ads to the visitors based on their visits to this site and any other sites on the Internet. 

You can opt out of the DART cookies if you visit the Google ad and content network Privacy Policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> Tracking of visitors through the DART cookie mechanisms is the subject to Google’s Privacy Policy.

Other third party ad servers/networks may also use cookies to track the users’ browsing and activities on this site to measure the total advertising effectiveness, and the other reasons provided in their own Privacy Policies. Amerikanki.com doesn’t have access and control over these cookies that might be used by the third party advertisers.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
When visiting Amerikanki.com, the IP address used to access the website will be logged as well as the date and time of access. The information is used to only track users movement, analyze trends, administer the website, and collect demographic information for our internal statistical use. The most important thing is that your IP address isn’t linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links to Third Party Websites**  
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the Privacy Policies on these websites. You should be aware that the Privacy Policies of these sites may differ from our own.
